https://lvaccident.com/privacy-policy/

Case Results
$230,000. Settlement for a hotel guest who contracted an infectious disease as a result of a hotel’s improperly maintained water[…]
read more
$113,000. Jury verdict for meniscus knee surgery repair caused by motor vehicle collision. Adverse insurance company disputed our client’s damages[…]
read more
$200,000. Settlement at mediation for a woman who fell on a raised floor outlet at a store. She required home[…]
read more
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to information collected online
from users of this website and to any user information collected via other
sources. In this policy, we outline what kind of information we collect, when
and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the
choices you have with respect to your personal information.
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE AND HOW IS IT USED?
When we collect information from our users, it is most often
via a form on this website. These forms include contact request forms,
scholarship entry forms, and requests for more information. Any contact
information submitted via a form on this site may be used to contact you regarding
services, events, or other offerings made available by constituents. We don’t
solicit or release any of the information you provide, unless we say so in this
Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
User-supplied information:
If you fill out a contact form on this website, we may ask you to provide
personal information that may include (but may not be limited to) e-mail
address, name, phone number and state. If chat is available through this site,
you may be asked to provide information if you participate in an online chat.
Please do not submit any confidential, proprietary or sensitive personally
identifiable information (e.g. Social Security Number; date of birth; drivers
license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial information)
(collectively, “Sensitive Information”). If you submit any Sensitive
Information, you do so at your own risk and we will not be liable to you or
responsible for consequences of your submission.
Information that you provide to us through the contact form
or an online chat will be used so that we may respond to your inquiry. We may
also use information you provide to us to communicate with you in the future.
If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt out (unsubscribe)
as described below.
Web server logs:
When you visit our website, we may track information about your visit and store
that information in web server logs, which are records of the activities on our
sites.
The servers automatically capture and save the information
electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include:
your unique Internet protocol address;the name of your unique Internet service
provider;the town/city, county/state and country from
which you access our website;the kind of browser or computer you use;the number of links you click within the site;the date and time of your visit;the web page from which you arrived to our site;the pages you viewed on the site; andcertain searches/queries that you conducted via
our website(s).
The information we collect in web server logs helps us
administer the site, analyze its usage, protect the website and its content
from inappropriate use, and improve the user’s experience.
Cookies: In order
to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our websites and
applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you.
Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a
Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help
remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits.
Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won’t have to
re-enter them each time you visit.
The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are
initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your
browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept
cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not
function properly if you don’t accept cookies.
If you wish to disable cookies from this site, you can do so
using your browser. You should understand that some features of many sites may
not function properly if you don’t accept cookies. For more information about
using browsers to manage cookies, please see All About Cookies. You can also
refuse to accept Flash cookies from this website using Adobe’s Flash management
tools. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ad
Settings.
By visiting this website, you consent to the use of cookies
and similar technologies in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
Third-party Services:
We may use services hosted by third parties, including Adobe Site Catalyst, to
assist in providing our services and to help us understand the use of our site
by our visitors. These services may collect information sent by your browser as
part of a web page request, including your IP address or cookies. If these
third-party services collect information, they do so anonymously and in the
aggregate to provide information helpful to us such as website trends, without
identifying individual visitors.
In addition, we may use services provided by third parties
to display relevant content, products, services and advertising to you. These
third parties may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect
or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the internet. They
may then use that information to provide measurement services so we can
understand your interests and retarget advertisements based on your previous
visits to this website. Please keep in mind that we do not share your personal
information with any third-party advertiser, ad server or ad network.
You may be able to opt-out of the collection and use of
information for ad targeting by some third parties by visiting
www.aboutads.info/choices. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by
visiting Google’s Ad Settings. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll’s
and their partners’ targeted advertising. Please see “Cookies” in the section
above for more information on how you can control the use of cookies on your
computer.
California Do Not
Track: Our web services do not alter, change, or respond upon receiving Do
Not Track (DNT) requests or signals in browsers. As described in more detail
above, we track user activity using web server logs, cookies and similar
technologies. Information collected in web server logs helps us analyze website
usage and improve the user’s experience. Cookies allow us to offer you a
customized experience and present relevant advertising to you.
HOW IS PERSONAL INFORMATION PROTECTED?
We take certain appropriate security measures to help
protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized
access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized
persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user
data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any
unaffiliated parties, except as follows:
to agents, website vendors and/or contractors
who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us;if we are unable to assist with your matter, but
know an unaffiliated attorney or firm that may be able to help you, we may
refer you and share information you provided us with that party; andas required by law, in a matter of public safety
or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets
(for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during
bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data
is necessary to protect our rights or property.
HOW CAN I CORRECT, AMEND OR DELETE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR OPT OUT OF FUTURE COMMUNICATIONS?
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.
Contact us via the phone number listed on our website, our contact form, or
mailing address at any time to:
see what data we have about you, if any;change/correct any data we have about you;ask us to delete any data we have about you;
and/oropt out of future communications from us.
QUESTIONS?
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this
privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing
address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a
significant way, we will post the policy changes here.
If you have been injured, contact us today.
Free Initial Consultation
No Fee Unless We Recover Money on your Behalf
.
What is the fifth letter of the alphabet?
